<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FinStatInsight.com</title>
    <link>https://finstatinsight.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on FinStatInsight.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 15:01:35 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finstatinsight.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mercury Securities Q4-2023 Profit Before Tax (PBT) Decline to RM 667K Amidst Listing Expenses Impacting RM 3.9M</title>
      <link>https://finstatinsight.com/posts/mercury-securities-q4-2023-pbt-decline-to-rm-667k-amidst-listing-expenses-impacting-rm-3.9m/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finstatinsight.com/posts/mercury-securities-q4-2023-pbt-decline-to-rm-667k-amidst-listing-expenses-impacting-rm-3.9m/</guid>
      <description>Mercury Securities Berhad Q4-2023 Summary In the current quarter Q4-2023 concluding on October 31, 2023, Mercury Securities Berhad achieved a revenue of RM8.71 million which mainly from these 2 segments below.
Stockbroking segment recorded a revenue of RM6.35 million (72.90%) in the current financial quarter. The 72.90% revenue of the Stockbroking segment are derived from:
31.10.2023 Brokerage fees 3,681,320 Margin income 1,744,914 Underwriting and Placement Fees 915,148 Nominees fees 4,975 Total 6,346,357 Corporate Finance segment contributed revenue of RM2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cengild Medical Berhad Q1 2024 Revenue 11% Growth vs Preceding Quarter.</title>
      <link>https://finstatinsight.com/posts/cengild-medical-berhad-q1-2024-revenue-growth-vs-preceding-quarter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finstatinsight.com/posts/cengild-medical-berhad-q1-2024-revenue-growth-vs-preceding-quarter/</guid>
      <description>Cengild Medical Berhad Q1-2024 Summary In the current quarter Q1-2024 concluding on September 30, 2023, Cengild Medical Berhad achieved a revenue of RM17.60 million. This marks a notable growth of RM1.83 million, equivalent to 11.62%, when juxtaposed with the preceding quarter concluding on June 30, 2023, which reported revenue of RM15.77 million. The upswing in revenue can be primarily attributed to the heightened volume of patients, leading to an augmentation in both endoscopic procedures and surgeries conducted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DC Healthcare Holdings Q3 2023 Financial Loss Due to Higher Administrative Expenses</title>
      <link>https://finstatinsight.com/posts/dc-healthcare-q3-2023-financial-loss-due-to-higher-administrative-expenses/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finstatinsight.com/posts/dc-healthcare-q3-2023-financial-loss-due-to-higher-administrative-expenses/</guid>
      <description>Q3-2023 Summary Revenue: The Group reported a revenue of RM15.52 million for the current financial quarter, with a significant focus on aesthetic services, contributing approximately 84.28% of the total revenue.
Below is the chart &amp;amp; table showing the segmental analysis of the group&amp;rsquo;s revenue for the past 3 quarters.
Quarters 2023-Q1 2023-Q2 2023-Q3 Items 3/31/2023 6/30/2023 9/30/2023 Aesthetic services 14,930 15,923 13,074 General medical services 1,379 1,432 1,804 Sale of skincare products 502 537 635 Total 16,811 17,892 15,513 Loss Before Tax: Despite the revenue generated, the Group recorded a loss before tax amounting to RM3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oppstar Berhad Q2 2024 Recorded 36,31% Profit Before Tax (PBT) Margin</title>
      <link>https://finstatinsight.com/posts/oppstar-berhad-q2-2024-recorded-36-profit-before-tax-margin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finstatinsight.com/posts/oppstar-berhad-q2-2024-recorded-36-profit-before-tax-margin/</guid>
      <description>Oppstar Berhad Q2-2024 Summary In the current quarter, Oppstar Berhad achieved a noteworthy revenue of around RM14.03 million, contributing to a robust financial period with a total revenue of RM29.71 million.
During this quarter, turnkey design services played a pivotal role, contributing approximately RM9.51 million, constituting about 67.82% of the Group&amp;rsquo;s total revenue. Notably, these projects hailed from customers in the Northeast and Southeast Asian region, showcasing the Group&amp;rsquo;s regional presence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://finstatinsight.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finstatinsight.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to FinStatInsight.com About Us Welcome to FinStatInsight.com, your ultimate destination for in-depth financial analysis within the dynamic landscape of Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s corporate realm. I&amp;rsquo;m Chan, the founder and chief analyst, dedicated to providing you with unparalleled insights into the heart of Malaysia financial markets.
Our Core Focus FinStatInsight zeroes in on fundamental analysis, meticulously dissecting the intricate details of Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s prominent companies. We firmly believe in the power of comprehending financial statements to unlock the true potential of investments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive Financial Report</title>
      <link>https://finstatinsight.com/comprehensive-financial-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finstatinsight.com/comprehensive-financial-report/</guid>
      <description>FinStatInsight Comprehensive Financial Report: In order to facilitate a thorough understanding of the group&amp;rsquo;s financial standing, we present a comprehensive financial report analysis. This examination is underpinned by a detailed review of both quarterly and yearly financial data, complemented by trend charts that offer a visual representation of key financial indicators.
Quarterly &amp;amp; Yearly Financial Overview: Revenue Trends: The analysis delves into the quarterly / yearly revenue figures, identifying patterns and fluctuations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://finstatinsight.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finstatinsight.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Have a question or want to collaborate on guest posts related to Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s company finance fundamentals, sentiments or trends? We&amp;rsquo;d love to hear from you! Drop us a message, and our team at FinStatInsight.com will get back to you promptly. Your insights and inquiries are invaluable to us. Let&amp;rsquo;s connect and explore the world of Malaysian company market together through well informed financial fundamental analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Comprehensive Financial Reports &amp; In-depth Analysis</title>
      <link>https://finstatinsight.com/detail-financial-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finstatinsight.com/detail-financial-data/</guid>
      <description>Comprehensive Financial Reports from FinStatInsight.com We provided comprehensive financial reports sections, beyond the surface to provide detailed insights into companies&amp;rsquo; financial performance.
Detailed Profit and Loss Insights:
Explore the intricacies of profit and loss statements. Uncover nuances that drive a company&amp;rsquo;s revenue and expenses. In-depth analysis for a comprehensive understanding of financial performance. Financial Positions Demystified:
Gain insights into assets, liabilities, and equity shaping a company&amp;rsquo;s standing. Delve into the complexities of financial positions for stability and growth insights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Term of Use</title>
      <link>https://finstatinsight.com/term-of-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finstatinsight.com/term-of-use/</guid>
      <description>Terms of Use Welcome to FinStatInsight.com
By accessing and using our website, you agree to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use. Please read these Terms of Use carefully before using our website and service related to finance analysis and compancy fundamental analysis.
1. Acceptance of Terms By accessing or using our website, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound by these Terms of Use.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
